Guide to the Alvin A. Achenbaum Papers, 1948-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Grey Advertising, 1955-1974 and undated
  - General Files
    - General Administrative Efficiency, 1967 (Box GR21)
    - Grey Matter (newsletter), 1962-1974 (Box GR21)
    - Grey organization, 1971 (Box GR21)
    - Guide to Marketing Planning at Grey, 1963 (Box GR21)
    - How Advertising Works, 1968 (Box GR21)
    - Inter-Departmental Relationships, 1967 (Box GR21)
    - International Task Force Report to Management, 1967 (Box GR21)
    - Judgmental Scales, 1965 (Box GR21)
    - Leon Festinger, 1964-1965 (Box GR21)
    - Market testing, 1961-1972, (4 folders) (Box GR22)
    - Market testing case studies, 1958-1960 (Box GR22)
    - Marketing Planning at Grey, 1956, 1960, (2 folders) (Box GR22)
    - Marketing Planning Guide, 1960-1967, (3 folders) (Box GR22)
    - Marketing Procedures and Formats, 1968 (Box GR22)
    - Marketing testing, 1962-1963 (Box GR23)
    - New business and acquisitions, 1967 (Box GR23)
    - New product research, 1955-1967, (2 folders) (Box GR23)
    - Operating Manual for the Preparation of a Background Analysis, 1964 (Box GR23)
    - Personnel: Organization, Policy and Human Relations, 1967 (Box GR23)
    - Psychological/Motivational research, 1955-1960, (2 folders) (Box GR23)
    - Sales projections, 1961 (Box GR24)
    - Selected Financial Data, 1971 (Box GR24)
    - Seminar on Attitude Measurement, 1963-1964 (Box GR24)
    - Seminars on market target/buying incentives, 1964-1966 (Box GR24)
    - Sense and Nonsense in Creative Research, 1962 (Box GR24)
    - Status of Community Antenna Television, 1968 (Box GR24)
    - Taking the Magic out of Magic Number Copy Research (by Shirley Young), 1971 (Box GR24)
- J. Walter Thompson Company, 1955-1986 and undated
  - Advertising: Manipulation or Persuasion?, circa 1970s (Box GR24)
  - Allocating Advertising Weight Geographically, undated (Box GR24)
  - An Advertising Outlook (Dan Seymour speech), 1973 (Box GR24)
  - An Up-to-Date Look at the Strategy and Tactics of Couponing and Sampling in the Packaged Goods Industry, 1969 (Box GR24)
  - Basis for the Formulation of a Marketing Plan for JWT (Domestic) (by Nariman Dhalla), 1973 (Box GR24)
  - Checkerboard Tests: Clorets, 1972-1973 (Box GR24)
  - Clorets 1973 Media Spending and Test Translation Costs, 1973 (Box GR24)
  - Copy Testing--Does Anyone Have the Answers?, 1972 (Box GR24)
  - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box GR25)
  - Does Advertising Manipulate Consumer Behavior?, 1971 (Box GR25)
  - Effective reach and exposure, 1973-1976 (Box GR25)
  - Fact or Fiction about Prime Time TV Communication, 1973 (Box GR25)
  - Future of the Advertising Agency Research Function (by Rena Bartos), 1974 (Box GR25)
  - How to Introduce and Successful New Brand, 1973 (Box GR25)
  - JWT Corporate (Harry Clark speech), 1974 (Box GR25)
  - JWT Target Plan for Holiday Inn U.S. System Advertising, 1974 (Box GR25)
  - New product development, 1973-1982 and undated (Box GR25)
  - New York Office 1972 Annual Marketing Plan, 1972 (Box GR25)
  - Our Creative Disciplines (Burt Manning speech), undated (Box GR25)
  - Positioning presentation for Quaker cereals (by Marketing Corporation of America), 1986 (Box GR25)
  - Questions and Answers in Planning Advertising (T-Plan), undated (Box GR25)
  - Role of Market Communication in Selling Automobiles, 1971 (Box GR26)
  - Segmentation Study of the Dentrifice Market, 1973 (Box GR26)
  - Strategic planning, 1955-1972 (Box GR26)
  - Strategic Planning Study of the Dog Food Market, 1973 (Box GR26)
  - Target Planning System, 1971-1973 (Box GR26)
  - Test Market Evaluation Bulletin, 1970 Oct. (Box GR26)
  - Trouble at Credibility Gap (Arnold Grisman), circa 1973 (Box GR26)
  - Warner Lambert--A Proposal for Testing Day vs. Night-Time Television Using the Checkerboard Test Design, 1972, (2 folders) (Box GR26)
  - What Will the Advertising Business Be Like in 5-6 Years (Nariman Dhalla), 1974 (Box GR26)
- Large-Format Materials
  - General Files
    - Advertising compensation data, circa 1978 (Box OV1)
    - Taking Behavioralism Seriously (John Hanson and Douglas Kyser), undated (Box OV1)
  - Achenbaum Bogda
    - GTE residential telephone survey forms, 1995, (2 folders) (Box OV1)
    - Hyundai collateral literature, 1997 (Box OV1)
    - Robert Coen Presentation on Advertising Expenditures, 1992-2002 (Box OV1)
  - Backer Spielvogel Bates
    - Miller advertising timeline, 1970-1983, circa 1983 (Box OV1)
  - Canter Achenbaum
    - New Product Ideas for Gelatin, undated (Box OV1)
    - Nissan/Datsun clippings, 1977-1987 (Box OV1)
    - Scott Paper agency performance evaluation, 1988 (Box OV1)
    - Toyota Mid-80s Product Policies and Direction, 1980 (Box OV1)
  - Grey Advertising
    - Sales conviction interview sheets, 1956-1957 (Box OV1)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company
    - Questions and Answers in Planning Advertising (T-Plan), 1972 (Box OV1)
    - Strategic Positioning--London vs. New York T-Plans, circa 1972 (Box OV1)
  - MARC (Marketing and Research Counselors)
    - National Automobile Survey forms, circa 1978 (Box OV2)
    - National Automobile Survey visual aids, undated (Box OV2)
  - Writings and Speeches
    - Transformation speech, hard copies of charts, undated (Box OV2)
    - New Marketing Environment presentations transparencies, undated (Box OV3)
    - Agency evaluation forms, undated (Box OV4)
    - Advertising Age 50 Years of TV Advertising collectors' edition, 1995 Spring (Box OV4)
    - Interactive advertising printed materials, 1999-2000 (Box OV4)
    - Schematic of the Market Research Method for Conducting Market Target/Buying Incentive Studies, chart, undated (Box OV4)
  - Achenbaum Bogda
    - Integrity Music creative, 1993-1996 and undated (Box OV4)
  - Canter Achenbaum
    - AMI presentation flow charts, undated (Box OV4)
    - Magnavox trend data, 1973 (Box OV4)
    - Minolta print advertising (Campbell Mithun Esty), 1993 (Box OV4)
    - Nissan Pulsar brochure (in Japanese), 1987 (Box OV4)
    - Simupac, 1976-1978 (Box OV4)
    - Toyota--Wharton econometric data, 1980 (Box OV4)
- Writings and Speeches, 1948-2011 and undated
  - Articles, Speeches, Presentations
    - 1980: The Threshold to the Future Decade, 1979 (Box WS1)
    - Achenbaum at Large (Adweek Marketing Week), 1985-1987 (Box WS1)
    - Achenbaum's Analysis (Advertising Age), 1989 (Box WS1)
    - Achenbaum Tells About Picking an Ad Agency, Toyota, Datsun Style, undated (Box WS1)
    - Ad crisis, draft, undated (Box WS1)
    - Ad Venture (Credits magazine), 1986 (Box WS1)
    - Addressing the Market Information Malaise, 1995 (Box WS1)
    - Addressing the New Advertising Environment, 1988 (Box WS1)
    - Advertising Agency Homogenization, 1983 (Box WS1)
    - Advertising Agency of the Future, 1994 (Box WS1)
    - Advertising Agency of Tomorrow, 1991 (Box WS1)
    - Advertising book, brand chapter notes and drafts, 1993-1995, (2 folders) (Box WS1)
    - Advertising book, overview chapter, 1993 (Box WS2)
    - Advertising book, proposal, 1993 (Box WS2)
    - Advertising book, Richard Lessler files, 1994 (Box WS2)
    - Advertising Doesn't Manipulate Consumers, 1972 (Box WS2)
    - Advertising in the Changing Pattern of Distribution, 1951 (Box WS2)
    - Advertising Environment of the 90s, 1992, (3 folders) (Box WS2)
    - Advertising is Broken--Can It Be Fixed?, 2004, (1-2 of 5 folders) (Box WS2)
    - Advertising is Broken--Can It Be Fixed?, 2004, (3-5 of 5 folders) (Box WS3)
    - Advertising is Broken--Why Fix It?, 2007 (Box WS3)
    - Advertising: Manipulation or Persuasion?, undated (Box WS3)
    - Advertising/Promotion Budgets (speech given by F. Kent Mitchell), 1985 (Box WS3)
    - Advertising's Future Prediction (speech given by Marion Harper), 1952-1972 (Box WS3)
    - Agency/Client Relationships, 1989 (Box WS3)
    - Agency Compensation, undated (Box WS3)
    - Agency of the Future, 1994 (Box WS3)
    - Agency relations position paper, 1976 (Box WS3)
    - American Marketplace and Where It Is Headed in the Next Five Years, 1990 (Box WS3)
    - Answer to One of the Unanswered Questions About the Measurement of Advertising Effectiveness, 1966 (Box WS3)
    - Are Brands Bankrupt?, 1993 (Box WS3)
    - Are We Executing or Killing Our Marketing Plans?, 1982 (Box WS3)
    - Attitude Research Revisited, 1989 (Box WS3)
    - Brand Driven Marketing Communications, 1990 (Box WS3)
    - Brand Equity Is Only a Piece of the Puzzle, 1996 (Box WS3)
    - Brand Management, draft, undated (Box WS4)
    - Branding article, notes and drafts, 1952-1990 (Box WS4)
    - Branding in the New Market Environment, 1991 (Box WS4)
    - Branding white paper--The New Marketing of Brands, 1990 (Box WS4)
    - Brief remarks, AAPOR conference, 1965 (Box WS4)
    - Campbell Soup Food Marketing--Bringing It All Together, undated (Box WS4)
    - Can Advertising Be Tested in the Marketplace?, 1981 (Box WS4)
    - Can Magazines Play a Role in Stabilizing TV Prices?, 1977 (Box WS4)
    - Can Network Commercial Scheduling within a Program Be Improved?, 1973 (Box WS4)
    - Can the Brand Management System Adapt to the New Marketing Environment?, 1988 (Box WS4)
    - Can We Tolerate a Double Standard in Marketing Research?, 1984-1985 (Box WS4)
    - Cardinal Sins of Agency Management, 1978 (Box WS4)
    - Changing Advertising Agencies: A Most Ingenious Paradox, 1977 (Box WS4)
    - Compensation Philosophy: The Client View, 1989 (Box WS4)
    - Concept of Effective Reach, 1973 (Box WS4)
    - Concept of Market Segmentation, 1955 (Box WS4)
    - Consumer Attitudes: Do They Matter in Advertising?, undated (Box WS5)
    - Consumer Attitudes Toward Health and Soup, 1991 (Box WS5)
    - Copy Research: TV Commercial Testing Program, 1959 (Box WS5)
    - Craps or Poker: Gambling on New Market Entries, 1992 (Box WS5)
    - Crisis in Advertising and How to Fix It, 2004 (Box WS5)
    - Crisis in Advertising: Does It Matter?, 1973-2003 and undated, (2 folders) (Box WS5)
    - Criteria for Developing and Evaluating Commercial Testing Techniques, 1966 (Box WS5)
    - Dawn of Competition in the Advertising Business, 1987 (Box WS5)
    - Declining Power of National Advertising, undated (Box WS5)
    - Desensitization of America, 1976 (Box WS5)
    - Developing New Market Entries, undated (Box WS5)
    - Disposal Revolution: The Role Advertising Can Play, 1991 (Box WS5)
    - Does Advertising Manipulate Consumer Behavior?, 1971, (2 folders) (Box WS5)
    - Does Marketing Need a CPR?, 1977 (Box WS6)
    - Dominant TV Has Vulnerable Underbelly, 1978 (Box WS6)
    - Dunkin' Donuts branding presentation, 2000, (2 folders) (Box WS6)
    - E-commerce article, 1999 (Box WS6)
    - Effective Exposure: A New Way of Evaluating Media, 1977 (Box WS6)
    - Effective exposure early paper, 1973 or 1974 (Box WS6)
    - Effective Exposure in Media Planning, 1976 (Box WS6)
    - Effective Exposure: The Subversion of a Useful Idea, 1986 (Box WS6)
    - Effie Awards introductory remarks, 1979 (Box WS6)
    - Eight Marketing Lessons from George Bush, 1988 (Box WS6)
    - Enhancing Advertising Productivity, 1991 (Box WS6)
    - Escaping from a Sea of Trouble, 1976 (Box WS6)
    - Evolving Network Television Market, 1985 (Box WS6)
    - Excuse Me, Mr. McCluhan, But Now the Retail Store Is the Message, 1997 (Box WS6)
    - Expanding Services in Marketing, 1990 (Box WS6)
    - Facing the New Media Reality, 1977 (Box WS6)
    - Fact or Fiction about Prime-Time Communication, 1973 (Box WS7)
    - Fear Factor, 1985 (Box WS7)
    - Five Easy Ways to Increase Advertising Productivity, 1993 (Box WS7)
    - FTC research rule, 1977 (Box WS7)
    - Future Challenge to Market Research, 1986-1993 (Box WS7)
    - Future of the Advertising Business, drafts, undated (Box WS7)
    - Future of Marketing Research, 1986-2003 (Box WS7)
    - Gresham's Law of Research, 1971-1986 (Box WS7)
    - Has Advertising Lost Its Bite?, notes and drafts, undated (Box WS7)
    - Hope and Opportunity, 1971 (Box WS7)
    - How Change in Our Demography and Social Structure Will Affect Marketing in the Next Few Years, 1985 (Box WS7)
    - How Change in Our Demography and Social Structure Will Affect Marketing in the Next 5-6 Years, 1979 (Box WS8)
    - How Change in Our Demography and Social Structure Will Affect the Media Situation in the Next Decade, 1979 (Box WS8)
    - How I Would Select an Advertising Agency, 1988 (Box WS8)
    - How National Consumer Advertising Benefits the Consumer, circa 1974 (Box WS8)
    - How Research Can Help in the Strategic Positioning of a Brand, 1973 (Box WS8)
    - How Research Can Work to Help Position a Brand, 1973 (Box WS8)
    - How Should the Brand Management System Be Modified to Adapt to the New Marketing Environment, 1990 (Box WS8)
    - How to Change Advertising Agencies, circa 1983 (Box WS8)
    - How to Choose an Advertising Agency, 1983 (Box WS8)
    - How to Help Your Brand Managers Manage Their Advertising More Effectively, undated (Box WS8)
    - Impending Media Crisis, 1979 (Box WS8)
    - Impending Media Crisis and What Should Be Done About It, 1978 (Box WS8)
    - Impending Media Crisis, originals, notes and miscellaneous, 1978 (Box WS8)
    - Implications of Price Competition on Brands, Advertising and the Economy, 1992 (Box WS8)
    - In Memory of Betty Macina, undated (Box WS8)
    - Increasing Advertising Productivity, 1996 (Box WS8)
    - Increasing Marketing Productivity, 1988 (Box WS8)
    - Increasing the Productivity of Your Advertising Dollars, 1989 (Box WS8)
    - Industry Consolidation and Its Impact on Branding, 1998 (Box WS8)
    - Insight--Achenbaum (Advertising Age), 1989 (Box WS9)
    - Introductory and concluding remarks, ARF conference, 1963 (Box WS9)
    - Introductory remarks, Marco Island, footwear industry, undated (Box WS9)
    - Is Advertising Accountability a Reality?, 1964 (Box WS9)
    - Is Advertising Manipulating the Consumer?, 1973-1975 (Box WS9)
    - Is Copy Testing a Predictive Tool?, 1964 (Box WS9)
    - Is Test Marketing on the Way Out?, 1983 (Box WS9)
    - Is the Brand Management System Obsolete?, 1988 (Box WS9)
    - Is the Government Our Only Problem?, 1971 (Box WS9)
    - Is There a Better Way for Goodyear to Use Magazines?, undated (Box WS9)
    - Knowledge Is a Thing Called Measurement, 1966 (Box WS9)
    - Magic Ingredient in New Product Development, 1968 (Box WS9)
    - Market Research's Next Major Challenge, 1986 (Box WS9)
    - Market segmentation course, 1955-1973 (Box WS9)
    - Market testing article, 1968-1972 (Box WS9)
    - Market Testing: Using the Market as a Laboratory, 1972 (Box WS9)
    - Marketing and research seminars on attitude measurement, 1963-1964 (Box WS10)
    - Marketing definitions article, 1948-2005, (3 folders) (Box WS10)
    - Marketing Food Products in the New Market Environment, 1988 (Box WS10)
    - Marketing Intelligence to Improve Decision-Making in the New Environment, 1989 (Box WS10)
    - Marketing Matters (column), 1996-1997 (Box WS10)
    - Marketing Opportunity for Financial Services, 1986 (Box WS10)
    - Marketing planning course, 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box WS10)
    - Marketing: What It Is and How It Should Be Practiced, 2008 (Box WS11)
    - Marketing's Challenge for the Future, 1990 (Box WS11)
    - Maximizing Advertising Agency Productivity, 1981 (Box WS11)
    - Maximizing Agency Productivity, 1978 (Box WS11)
    - Media Challenge, 1986 (Box WS11)
    - Media Effectiveness, 1976-1981 (Box WS11)
    - Media's New Leverage, 1977-1978 (Box WS11)
    - Miscellaneous drafts of articles, 1978-1981 (Box WS11)
    - Mismanagement of Brand Equity, 1993 (Box WS11)
    - Must Television Continue to Dominate the Media Scene?, 1978 (Box WS11)
    - Must We Test Advertising to Death?, 1980 (Box WS11)
    - National Checkerboard Research Design, undated (Box WS11)
    - Negotiated Fee, 1976 (Box WS11)
    - Network television paper, undated (Box WS12)
    - New compensation article, undated (Box WS12)
    - New Market Entries: Lifeblood or Albatross?, 1974 (Box WS12)
    - New Market Entries: Their Identification and Evaluation, undated (Box WS12)
    - New Marketing Entries: Lifeblood or Albatross?, 1990 (Box WS12)
    - New Perspective: Brand Driven Marketing Communications, 1990 (Box WS12)
    - New Perspective for BSBW, 1990 (Box WS12)
    - New Perspective on the Use of Media and Its Differential Role in Automobile Advertising, 1990, (2 folders) (Box WS12)
    - Objective Approach to the Problem of Market Segmentation, 1964 (Box WS12)
    - Panel on media weighting, 1977 (Box WS12)
    - Perils in Niche Marketing, 1986 (Box WS12)
    - Photographic Advertising: Is It Doing Its Job Today?, 1987 (Box WS12)
    - Play It Again, Brand, 1990 (Box WS12)
    - Playing Craps with New Market Entries, 1987 (Box WS12)
    - Position paper on escalating TV production costs, undated (Box WS12)
    - Possible white paper topics, undated (Box WS12)
    - Practical MBO (management by objective) Linkages, 1979 (Box WS12)
    - Pre-Evaluating Copy Effectiveness, 1962 (Box WS13)
    - Price By Any Other Name Is Still a Price, 1989 (Box WS13)
    - Price Discount By Any Other Name Is Still a Price Discount, 1985 (Box WS13)
    - Pricing paper, undated (Box WS13)
    - Program for Successful Launching of New Market Entries, undated (Box WS13)
    - Proposal to Obtain a Publisher/Distributor to Market a Unique Lecture Series on the Practice of Marketing, 2009 (Box WS13)
    - Pulling Away from Push Marketing, 1987 (Box WS13)
    - Purpose of Market Testing, 1965 (Box WS13)
    - Push marketing paper, 1985 (Box WS13)
    - Qualms Senior Management Have About Their Advertising Agencies, undated (Box WS13)
    - Relevant Measures of Consumer Attitudes, 1967 (Box WS13)
    - Remarks to IPG, 1989 (Box WS13)
    - Research's New Responsibility in a Consumerist Environment, 1971 (Box WS13)
    - Reshaping the Basis for Advertising Agency Compensation, 1988 (Box WS13)
    - Restoring Luster to Tarnished Brands, undated (Box WS14)
    - Retail Stores, Not E-Commerce, Will Dominate, 1999 (Box WS14)
    - Reversing the Advertising Productivity Crisis, 1992 (Box WS14)
    - Revising the Original Concept of Effective Exposure, 1994 (Box WS14)
    - Role of Brands in Commercial Advertising, 1995 (Box WS14)
    - Role of Market Research in the Future, 1986 (Box WS14)
    - Role of Research in the Development of Advertising Strategy, 1975 (Box WS14)
    - Round Research Pegs in Square Marketing Holes, 1988 (Box WS14)
    - Segmenting Markets, 1973 (Box WS14)
    - Service Economy, undated (Box WS14)
    - Statement before the FTC, 1971 (Box WS14)
    - Strategic marketing planning course, 1974 (Box WS14)
    - Strategic Positioning, 1975 (Box WS14)
    - Strategies for Addressing the New Market Environment, 1988 (Box WS14)
    - Study of the Demand for Network Television Time, undated (Box WS14)
    - Systematic Approach to Pre-Testing TV Commercials, 1963 (Box WS14)
    - Systematic Pre-Evaluation of TV Commercials, 1963 (Box WS15)
    - Television Commercial Testing Program, 1959 (Box WS15)
    - Ten Cardinal Sins in New Business Solicitation, 1990 (Box WS15)
    - Ten Impediments to Marketing Productivity, 1985 (Box WS15)
    - Test Marketing, 1984 (Box WS15)
    - Testing the Pulling Power of an Advertisement, undated (Box WS15)
    - The Seventies a Marketing View, 1971 (Box WS15)
    - These Prices Are Killing Us, undated (Box WS15)
    - Thirteen Ways to Make Your Advertising More Productive, 1978 (Box WS15)
    - To Do Is Not Necessarily to Know, 1971 (Box WS15)
    - Today's Consumer--Is Advertising Manipulating Her?, 1973 (Box WS15)
    - Toward a New Illiteracy, undated (Box WS15)
    - Traditional 15% Commission System Is Dead, Long Live the Equity Tailored Fee, 1976 (Box WS15)
    - Traditional Compensation Structures, 1997 (Box WS15)
    - Transformation of the Marketing Environment (for Philip Morris), undated (Box WS15)
    - Transformation of the Packaged Food Marketing Environment (Campbell's), 1990 (Box WS15)
    - Transformation of the Packaged Food Marketing Environment (General), 1990, (2 folders) (Box WS16)
    - Transformation of the Packaged Food Marketing Environment (Nestlé), 1990 (Box WS16)
    - Undervaluation of Brands and the Misuse of Advertising, 1990 (Box WS16)
    - University of South Florida talk, 1993 (Box WS16)
    - Use of Attitude Measurement in Testing TV Commercials, 1961 (Box WS16)
    - Usefulness of Market Testing as a Research Tool, 1963 (Box WS16)
    - Weighing Media Alternatives, 1977 (Box WS16)
    - What Do We Mean By Brand Driven Advertising?, undated (Box WS16)
    - What Does Research Tell Us About Advertising Copy Principles?, 1968 (Box WS16)
    - What the Advertising Business Will Be Like in 5 or 6 Years, 1978 (Box WS16)
    - What to Do About Copy Testing until the Millennium, 1966 (Box WS16)
    - What to Look for in Agency Compensation, 1996 (Box WS16)
    - What Will the Advertising Business Be Like in 5-6 Years?, 1976 (Box WS16)
    - What's in a Name?, 1990 (Box WS16)
    - What's Wrong with Advertising?, 1990-2003, (2 folders) (Box WS17)
    - When Good Research Goes Bad, 2001 (Box WS17)
    - Where Are Our Communications Consultants?, undated (Box WS17)
    - Who Says You Need Research to Position a Brand?, 1974 (Box WS17)
    - Why Advertisers Are Reassessing Their Agency Compensation Arrangements, 1986 (Box WS17)
    - Why Not a CPR for Survey Research?, 1976 (Box WS17)
    - Why the Need for New Products, undated (Box WS17)
    - Will the Advertising Agency Business Be Materially Different in the Next 5-6 years?, 1990 (Box WS17)
    - Will the Advertising/Marketing Communications Business Be Materially Different in the Next 5-6 years?, 1990 (Box WS17)
    - Your Ad Agency--Chameleon or Dinosaur?, 1988 (Box WS17)
  - Book Files
    - Agency search exhibit materials, undated (Box WS18)
    - Auxiliary marketing functions, 2010 (Box WS18)
    - Ch. 2, Sales Promotion, 2010 (Box WS18)
    - Ch. 3, Direct-Response Marketing, 2010 (Box WS18)
    - Ch. 4, Marketing Technology, 2010 (Box WS18)
    - Compensation exhibit materials, 1984-1989 (Box WS18)
    - Compensation notes, undated (Box WS18)
    - Introduction, 2008-2010, (2 folders) (Box WS18)
    - Marketing concepts notes, undated (Box WS18)
    - Marketing planning book, early attempt, undated, (2 folders) (Box WS18)
    - Vol. I Ch. 1: What is Marketing?, 2010, (2 folders) (Box WS18)
    - Vol. I Ch. 2: Competition, 2010, (2 folders) (Box WS19)
    - Vol. I Ch. 3: Definitions, 2010, (2 folders) (Box WS19)
    - Vol. I Ch. 4: History, 2010 (Box WS19)
    - Vol. V. Ch. 5: Role of Government, 2010 (Box WS19)
    - Achenbaum's history on the definition of marketing, undated (Box WS19)
    - Achenbaum's speeches used as source material, 1978-1998, (2 folders) (Box WS19)
    - Articles on advertising and marketing, 2005-2009 (Box WS19)
    - Content of course, notes, 2004 (Box WS19)
    - Definitions of marketing, undated, (2 folders) (Box WS19)
  - Lecture Series
    - Drafts of various parts, 2006-2008 and undated, (3 folders) (Box WS20)
    - DVDs/Internet/Technology articles, 2006-2007 (Box WS20)
    - Lecture A: Marketing and the Law, 1996 (Box WS20)
    - Lecture 1: What is Marketing, 2005 and undated, (3 folders) (Box WS20)
    - marketing planning notes, undated (Box WS21)
    - Miscellaneous ideas and notes, 2003 and undated, (3 folders) (Box WS21)
    - Part I: Exhibits and miscellaneous, undated (Box WS21)
    - Part I Section 1: Exhibits and miscellaneous, 2006-2008 and undated, (4 folders) (Box WS21)
    - Part I Section 1: Introduction, 2005 and undated, (4 folders) (Box WS21)
    - Part I Section 1: Introduction, 2006-2009 and undated, (10 folders) (Box WS22)
    - Part I Section 1: Introduction, final draft, 2005 (Box WS23)